[overlapping social media audio]
[overlapping social media audio
continues]
[man on video] Down
on the ground! I said
down on the ground!
[overlapping social media audio
continues]
[passionate moaning]
[passionate moaning continues]
You know you don't have
to watch until the end, right?
It's obviously porn...
just delete it and move on.
-I'm stalling.
-What's your count?
19.
You better move if you want
to hit your quota.
I'm just afraid of what's
going to pop up next.
-It's better porn than murder.
-Hmm?
It all sort of blends together.
[passionate moaning]
[sudden silence]
[mouse wheel scrolling]
[video/audio playing]
[woman in video
breathing heavily]
[woman screams; sharp thud]
[car alarm in video blares]
[mouse wheel scrolling]
The job is easy...
You sit at a desk,
you stare at a computer,
and you peruse social media,
which is what you probably do
all day anyways.
But here you'll be reviewing
posts that have been flagged
by users.
We call them tickets.
If a ticket violates our
corporate mandated
"Terms of Use"...
click delete.
If not, click approve.
That's it.
Some tickets are nonsense.
People being overly sensitive.
Others, well, they can be
impactful.
I will walk you through a few
examples.
Footage of a man killing a
rabbit is animal torture and
should be removed.
But footage of a man killing a
rabbit and then eating it
could be considered culinary
and should remain up.
Makes sense, right? Always
consider intent.
Does the post condemn or
support? Are we looking at
something real or fake?
Satire or sincerity?
Nuance is key.
The next ticket is a little
more complicated, so pay close
attention.
[loud clatter]
I've got an idea: why don't I
just burn the whole building
down?
I can make this fucking place
disappear.
All I need is some kerosene,
a box of matches,
and a can-do attitude!
Comments, questions, concerns?!
[loud clatter]
Should we do something? Calm
him down? Call security?
Hello...?
He does this stuff all the
time. It's how he copes.
To be honest, we're all kind of
annoyed that he never actually
follows through with it.
But welcome to the team,
by the way.
[various social media audio]
[doctor] If you're using
a tourniquet, don't tie it
too tightly.
Blood pressure is good
for making veins
appear in the skin,
but it also can push the needle
out, make it harder
for insertion.
[woman] Thank you, Aaron.
Another item that we know
prospective nurses
are always interested
in learning about
is just daily patient care...
Listen to this:
Is your name Chipotle?
Because I want to bury
my face in your taco.
I can't.
You know those apps don't
background check, right?
-So?
So, rapists use them.
Okay, well, I'm sweeping left
on rapists.
Looks like the overnight shift
enjoyed themselves again.
Jesus.
Like, do it in the bathroom or
your car.
Help yourself.
Thanks.
Daisy, you haven't
logged in yet.
-What the fuck?!
-I'm about to! I'm about to.
[overlapping social media audio]
[social media audio continues]
[voices shouting angrily]
[man] You get paid
to watch porn?
Not just porn, other things,
awful things.
Not the kind of stuff you want
to talk about on a first date.
Is everyone like horny all the
time?
Some people seem to be, yeah.
But it doesn't affect you?
Eh, also not the kind of thing
to get into on the first date.
Do you like it?
I mean, that's what matters.
Uh... It's not what I pictured
myself doing.
Just don't have any other
options at the moment.
If you could do any job
in the world...
what would it be?
A nurse.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Not an astronaut
or the president?
-No...
not interested,
not qualified for that.
So go be a nurse.
It's not that simple.
There's school and
applications and interviews
and a test.
Take the test?
I did.
still not a nurse.
Hmm.
Ha ha, yeah!
Okay? Huh?
Oh ho ho ho ho ho!
Ring!
What was that noise?
[glass shatters]
Where'd you get those?
Oh hey, uh, supply closet.
Wanna try?
-No, I'm good.
-Sure?
You go fuck yourself then...
Yeah!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Um...
Can you be more specific?
Why did you delete that video?
Which one?
Oh, it's violent and
disturbing, and the amount of
blood is gratuitous.
-It was pinned to a news site.
-So?
Come on, Daisy.
We could get sued!
Freedom of speech
is a real thing.
Okay, but freedom
of reach is not.
What the fuck does that mean?
The poor woman killed herself.
No one needs to see that.
Well, you don't write the
guidelines. You follow them.
Poorly.
Okay, well, sometimes the
guidelines are wrong.
You haven't been here
six months-- you're talking
out of your ass.
Next time you think you know
better, try to remember:
you don't.
In case you change your mind.
Before we get too deep into
anything today,
I want to clarify a few
changes to our revised
terms-of-use packet.
There's been some confusion
with a particular type of post,
and it's hurting our accuracy
rating.
Just because a ticket has a bad
word does not mean it has to
be removed.
Harassment or gratuitous
profanity should always be
deleted.
But users are allowed to curse
if the phrasing is "artistic,"
such as song lyrics,
or "commendatory"--
something like, You're my
favorite person.
Oh! Oh!
Yeah, Bob. Yes.
Yeah, "person" isn't a bad word.
It's a fill-in-the-blank sort
of thing. You get the point,
right?
No, I don't. What if I fill in
the blank with "asshole"?
-That's okay.
-What about "asshole toucher"?
Nope. Too sexual. You should
know that by now.
What about a racial slur?
All right, that's enough, Bob.
No, I'm being serious.
I come across this stuff all
the time, and I never know how
to handle it.
Like, what if I said, "You're
my favorite Mick," or "You're
my favorite dothead,"
or "You're my favorite
cheese-eating moosefucker,"
which is a term for
French-Canadian, I just made up.
You can't say any of that.
This is a workplace.
But if it were in a ticket, we
should approve it, right? Or...
Technically, none of those
words are on our current
banned phrases list.
Remember, we're not censors.
We are moderators.
[male voice]
Deep breath in...
[knock on door]
[man] ...hold it
for as long as you can.
Then deep breath out...
[knocking on door]
[sighs]
-Hello.
-Hey.
Can you keep an eye on Violet?
I got called into work.
Um, I'm like very in the
middle of something right now.
Yeah, I can, uh, smell it.
Okay, sure. Yeah, you can
bring her over.
Can you give me a second to,
like, clean up and open a
window?
-Good idea. Thanks!
-Yep.
You hungry?
Not really.
-Are you on Reddit?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, Reddit is for adults.
No, it's not.
Yeah, it is.
I've had an account
since I was 9.
Okay, um...
Okay, let's make a deal.
You can stay up as late as you
want, but no tablet and no
phone.
What's the point of staying up
late if I can't use my tablet?
Uh, unlimited movies
and popcorn?
-Can I have beer?
-No.
[Violet chuckles]
-Oh, my God.
-[laughter]
-Do you want your stars?
-Yes, please.
When I was your age,
all we had were glow-in-
the-dark stickers.
And they never worked.
It was actually kind of
eye-opening.
Like, the job sucks, but it
does protect people.
Yeah, like, knights in the
shiniest armor.
We watch this shit so no one
else has to, like little kids.
Yeah, kids annoy me,
but yeah, I get it.
Well, we're just like the
first responders of the
internet, you know?
That's like my silver lining
from now on, at least.
-I mean, it's a good
mindset to have.
-Do you think?
-Yeah.
-I mean, me too. I just...
I thought it when
I was violently high,
so I wasn't sure.
Oh, by the way, I never asked.
How was your date?
Oh, it was good.
I think he was cute. He's sweet.
-Then you should call him.
-Yeah, I should.
[overlapping social media audio]
[blade rasps]
[no audible speech]
This in... just so...
Here, take the tourniquet off.
There's too much blood
pressure. Makes it hard for
the needle to go in.
-I saw that on YouTube.
-Try to sit still, okay, ma'am?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
And we're in.
Do you like your job?
Sometimes.
Sure.
Do you see a lot of bad stuff?
Unfortunately, yeah.
Yes, I do.
Car crashes, overdoses.
But most of our patients are
obese people
who think they're having a
heart attack. So...
Did I have a heart attack?
No, sweetie, you didn't.
Okay, let's hook you up.
There we go. All set.
Mmm.
Trust me, you have
absolutely nothing to be
ashamed of.
Fainting is like a rite
of passage at Paladin.
We all do it at some point.
Everybody probably thinks I'm
a pussy now.
Come on, nobody thinks that.
And if they do, fuck them.
Literally, go sit on their
face and thrust.
'Cause next week, it will be
one of them on the floor for
sure.
I feel still foggy.
That's like a hangover.
It will pass.
You just need to get the bad
shit out of your system.
-How?
-Sleep it off.
How did I look when I fell?
Was it at least, like, cool
and dramatic?
Bob tried to give
you mouth-to-mouth,
and I almost let him.
That's how bad you looked.
I took a video
of the aftermath
whenever you're
ready to laugh about it.
Yeah, I'm not quite there yet,
but thank you for doing that.
It was fun. You were like:
[rapid gasps]
[crickets chirping]
[blade rasps]
[sharp gasp]
Hi, my name is Daisy Morris.
I just received an invoice for
$2,200.
[woman on phone] Okay, ma'am,
I need your insurance number.
No, my job does not offer
insurance, so I use Medicaid.
[woman] Then there is
not much that I can do.
Okay, but it's still $2,200.
How is that possible?
[woman] What we can do is...
[woman continues indistinctly]
Whoa, whoa, hold! An ambulance
ride is $900?
Why the fuck does it cost that
much?
[laughing]
Yeah.
Hey, Paul!
New guy, Paul!
What's your email?
Why?
Because I want to send you an
email, you fucking dope.
We're doing an office pool...
where we predict which one of
us is going to have the next
meltdown.
That's pretty cruel.
Something to pass the time.
Right now you're the favorite.
-Me?
-Yeah.
-Someone thinks
I'm going to piss my pants?
-Yeah, that was me.
Uh, you can't bet on yourselves.
Don't get any ideas.
You really are a dickhead.
Yeah, so, uh,
so are you in or out?
Paul? Out.
He's out.
Well, hello.
I figured you'd take
the day off.
I can't lose a shift.
I need the money.
You're right.
Goddamn it.
What?
Just my first ticket of the
morning is a beheading.
Oh, yeah.
I've seen that one.
It keeps popping back up.
I don't know why.
But the footage is a little
bit blurry, so not too bad,
right?
[man] In order to find peace,
you must tame your thoughts,
quiet your mind,
focus on your loves.
Big breath in.
Hold it for as long as you can.
And big breath out.
[man] Feel a sense of being
swell within your chest--
cradling, soothing.
And whatever's causing
stress in your life,
just forget about it.
Fuck you,
you podcast-making dick.
[man] In order to find peace,
you must tame your thoughts,
quiet your mind,
focus on your loves.
Big breath in.
Hold it for as long as you can.
[birdsong]
[ominous music rises]
I'm getting a contact high
just looking at you.
Sorry.
At least lie.
Do me the courtesy.
Okay, I'm not high.
I'm very tired.
What do you want?
I want to send the hammer
ticket to the police.
On what grounds?
Kidnapping, torture, rape.
How do you know the act wasn't
staged and consensual?
Do you think that girl wanted
a nail bashed into her?
This is a fetish video.
It's gross, yes.
But it's just cheap special
effects and bad acting.
Did you hear her scream?
Did you watch it?
Like, did you hear that?
Daisy, we've been through
this. If we go to the cops
and we are wrong,
that causes legal problems for
our parent company.
I will put it in writing
that this is coming
from me and not you,
not the company.
-No!
-It'll be fine.
You did your job,
you clicked delete.
-End of story.
-I need to do more.
Then go volunteer at
the shelter. Don't be
a martyr, okay?
And if this is bothering you
so much, talk to the counselor.
Really.
We received an anonymous
complaint about you.
Oh, yeah?
From who? Linda? Fucking
tattletale.
I... I just said it was
anonymous.
You can tell. Was it Linda?
Yeah?
Should I jump in to read it out?
Eh, give me the bullet points.
Well, your colleagues are
afraid of you, Bob.
'Cause I yell sometimes.
It's because of what you yell.
Look, work can be frustrating.
I get that, right?
But there has to be a better
way to manage how you feel.
Like what?
Well, use the tranquility room.
Yeah, when things get difficult
pop yourself in there for your
nine minutes of wellness time.
Mm.
-Mmm.
-Now, I know
nine minutes sounds...
...short, but if you clear
your head, you'd be surprised
how long it can feel.
Yeah?
You could try drawing
in a coloring book.
It can really
take your mind off things.
Yeah, yeah. I guess so...
coloring book, yeah.
You know, before I came here,
I watched a video of a kid
getting molested.
I had to watch it for 20
seconds because it's company
policy.
Before that it was two people
having sex on a dead body.
And before that it was some
fucking weirdo
funneling Mountain Dew
into his butt hole.
Do you really think a coloring
book is going to erase all
that from my memory?
To be honest, no, I don't.
Okay, I don't, but I do
believe that...
making some sort of sincere
effort might help.
Yeah.
You know, the people out there
who aren't yelling,
the ones
who are just taking it,
that's who you need to worry
about.
[mimics submachine gun fire]
[mimics shouting]
"I'm down here at Paladin..."
you get the idea."
I'm good... I'm good...
[overlapping social media audio]
[indistinct remark]
-[man shouts]
-[woman, calmly] I hate you.
[man 2] Women are inferior
by nature, and I don't care
if you disagree.
[woman 2] Fake tits,
fake lips and fake ass...
[overlapping social media audio]
[sirens wail]
Hi.
I'd like to report a crime.
[woman screaming]
Do you work at that place off
Route 90?
Paladin?
-No.
-Where'd you find this?
It popped up on my feed.
-Out of nowhere?
-Yeah, out of nowhere.
Was the footage filmed here in
Leon County or the state of
Florida?
I don't know.
Well, I can only
investigate crimes
that occur within
my jurisdiction.
Well, you can watch within
your jurisdiction.
That's not a crime.
Well, maybe it should be.
"I know it when I see it." You
ever hear that expression?
Supreme Court?
It was about porn. This is porn.
No, it's violence.
Even if this video is real,
which I very much doubt,
odds are these guys are worlds
away from here.
Who do I talk to, then?
Who is responsible
for things like this?
[sighs] Look.
I find this video disturbing,
like any average person would,
but that doesn't automatically
make it part of my purview.
-I wish there was
something I could do.
-You don't need to wish.
You're a police officer.
You can just go do something!
Unless there's a minor involved,
we can't arrest people for
things they watch with their
pants down.
We're not the jerk-off police.
Well, you could have fooled me.
I'm calling you a jerk-off,
in case that wasn't clear.
Yeah, I get it. Thanks.
What?
[Ava] I know!
I went to this bar where they
were doing this TikTok thing
where everyone had to wear
red, yellow, or green.
Red meant leave me the fuck
alone, yellow meant approach
me, but with caution,
and green meant come over and
annoy the shit out of me.
That sounds like a good system.
Yeah, except for the fact that
I was the only girl wearing
green,
so everybody was looking at me
like I had STDs reading on my
forehead.
I mean, isn't that why we go
out to meet people and
misbehave?
No, I came here to hang out
with you. I don't want to talk
to strangers.
Me too, but I want to have
a little bit of fun, and I could
use a partner in crime.
Nobody wants to be
a deviant alone.
I don't know, that sounds like
a tall ask for me right now.
No, it's not. You're 25,
you're good-looking,
just pick a guy and smile.
I don't want to hate
myself after.
Do you hate yourself right now?
A little bit.
So the worst-case scenario is
the status quo.
Drink it. It builds character.
It gives you charisma.
It gives you personality.
[beat-driven music plays]
[no audible speech]
[man grunting]
This... this doesn't feel right.
No, like, can you just push
it, push a little bit?
-OK, I'll move my leg.
Move away.
-Where?
-Oh, not good.
Not good, not good!
-Yeah, yeah. I agree.
Do you have KY?
No, I do not have KY.
This is not the '90s.
Well, I think I think
you might be dry.
OK.
I mean, that happens
to lots of girls.
It's the alcohol.
Don't sweat it.
Besides, we don't
have to have sex.
We could do, uh...
We could do... other stuff.
Are you kidding?
I mean, I came all the way
here in the middle of the night.
You can go!
-Seriously?
-Yep.
What's the Wi-Fi password?
I need to call an Uber.
Fuck you.
Is the "F" lowercase or capital?
Fuck!
[man] Bye.
[soft gasp]
[gasping]
[intriguing music rises]
Oh, what the fuck?
No, that's disgusting. Why
would you do that to yourself?
Hey, are you okay?
I just watched a guy, like,
cut his dick open
and eat a piece of it.
But I guess that's culinary,
though, and I should approve it.
Hey, hey, if you're gonna
throw up, try to actually do
it in a trash can
because they charge
for carpet cleaning here.
I just uh...
I just need some air.
Okay, well, lunch
is in 16 minutes, so just try
to hang on until then.
Not cool, Daisy.
He was about to drop.
I would have won the pool.
That's cheating!
So where were you
before Paladin?
Graduate school for computer
science and coding.
Holy shit, you are...
tragically overqualified
for this job.
In my spare time I've been
working on an algorithm that
can review tickets.
It, uh, tracks a percentage
of users that flag the post
and looks for trigger words
in the comment section.
It's pretty rudimentary, but...
They tried that,
but it didn't work.
This is one of the very few
times where people are more
reliable than computers.
That seems illogical.
Yeah, but computers
can't feel grief.
Which is technically
our only real job requirement,
if you think about it.
They're paying us for our pain.
That almost looks peaceful
lying there.
Yeah, almost.
What are you supposed to do
if it grabs a hold of you?
Fight. Yes.
I mean,
they're ambush predators,
so they're actually more
dangerous when you
can't see them.
That's how they get you.
Just like we practiced.
Let's try it, okay?
Grab the collar...
Push forward, use momentum
to drive that knee.
Knee, knee.
[audio continues indistinctly]
[plonk]
[toilet flushes]
[running footsteps]
Yeah, but "that" guy--
I ghosted him last week.
This guy I was talking
to at the bar,
I knew his ex-girlfriend.
We went to high school together.
But actually, I haven't spoken
to her in years.
I mean, she's just so fucking
annoying on Instagram.
She's just trying to be
this fitness influencer.
She just sucks.
And her arms are fat.
It's like, girl, go do some
push-ups, and then you
can influence me.
-You're not listening.
-Sorry.
Your turn to vent, I know.
I'm listening.
Vent? What do you mean, vent?
I don't give a fuck about
these people.
Vent!
[soft laughter]
-It's vodka. Little vodka?
-I'm all set, thanks.
Do you by chance have a gun
that I could borrow?
What?
For like a day or two.
Why do you think I own a gun?
You seem like a gun guy.
Go fuck yourself!
Go fuck yourself in the ass.
It's not an insult!
You talk about flamethrowers
and bombs every day.
-How is this an insult?
-That is totally...
different.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, I didn't realize.
A gun isn't the sort of thing
that people just lend each
other, anyway.
Well, I wouldn't know.
I've never even touched one.
I was going to...
People say it's therapeutic.
I was going to go to the range
and try it out.
Is this some sort of cry for
help?
'Cause honestly,
I-I got nothing.
No. It was just a favor,
if it wasn't too inconvenient.
Okay. I don't have a gun, Daisy.
-I don't have a gun.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
-Thanks anyways.
-Have a--
-Enjoy...
Thank you. You should do it.
Do what?
Shoot something.
Might feel good.
Okay.
[urgent music rises]
[urgent music continues]
[retching]
[girl screams]
[girl] Please don't!
Please, please, please don't!
[girl gasping]
[terrified screams]
[girl]
Somebody help!
Yes?
You're a fucking scumbag.
-[scoffs] Excuse me?
-You heard me.
Yeah, I have no idea why you
would say that to me.
-[hammer strikes nail]
-[woman] Aaahhh!
-What the fuck, lady!
-You made this!
-No, I didn't!
-You posted this!
You put this online for people!
-No, I fucking didn't!
-Then somebody
at your house did.
-Stay away from me!
-Why are you lying?
You fucking posted it!
Why are you lying?!
-You fucking posted this!
-I am not fucking lying!
You know who's a fucking
scumbag? You!
What are you doing shoving
that shit in my face?
You're sick!
[huffs]
[plonk]
Was grad school really hard?
It wasn't so bad,
but if you treat it like a job,
you can pretend you're in
college all over again, you
know.
Yeah.
Did you learn a lot?
-I hope so.
-[both laugh]
You're probably really good
with computers, then.
Isn't everyone our age?
Well, I just assume you can do
things that most people can't.
I guess.
Like, you think you could find
someone?
-Online?
-Yeah.
Like, their address or...
their job or just
information about them.
I mean, you don't really need
computer skills for that.
That's just basic
internet stalking.
[both laugh]
Well, the thing is, I only
know what he looks like.
I'm just asking for a name.
I know what you're asking for,
and I'm not doing it.
-Why?
-Because it's
stupid and dangerous.
For you to tell me a name?
-What happens after that?
-Nothing.
Then why do you
want it so badly?
I...
I just want to look him
in the eyes.
Okay, so I give you the name,
you look him in the eye.
Then what?
I'll just live happily
ever after.
Daisy, this guy's a maniac.
He will hurt you or worse.
-No, he won't.
-How do you know that?
Daisy, things
will get better, right?
Please, please!
Come on, name your price.
I will do anything! Anything...
Daisy, uh... I'm gay.
What?
-Like, I like dick.
-No!
Not sexually!
Not whoring myself out to you!
Okay, now you seriously
have to fucking help me
for being a dickhead.
Fuck... fuck.
-[hammer strikes nail]
-[woman] Aaahhh!
[Daisy gasps]
[sighs]
-[hammer strikes nail]
-[woman] Aaahhh! Aaaahhhh!
[Daisy sighs, sniffles]
[soft gasp]
[computer blurps]
What do you want?
Uh...
Another content moderator
had an episode.
This one was mild,
so I handled the fallout.
But it's probably time to
invest in an emergency kit
or a crash cart.
No, I just told you corporate
has their boots on our throats.
It's important
that they think Paladin
is nothing but smiling faces.
If they find out people
are keeling over,
they'll shut us down.
But we should keep our
employees safe while they're
punching our clock, right?
There won't be a clock to
punch if we piss off the
people that pay us.
-Do you want that
on your conscience?
-No, of course not.
You should organize a happy
hour for team bonding,
whatever the fuck it's called.
A little distraction should be
good for everyone.
Cash bar.
Okay, I mean, I
can arrange something
for next week so
you could join us.
Yeah. I'd rather
set myself on fire.
Yeah.
[Ava]
I'm dancing.
[laughter and chatter]
Alright guys, cheers.
How do you say it in Singapore?
Uh, jiak-sai.
-What does that mean?
-It means eat shit.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Okay,
eat shit, everybody.
-Jiak-Sai!
Did you just make up that name?
Okay, okay, Linda just bought
cocaine with Venmo.
What a world.
What a world!
[low, throbbing music]
[female vocalist sings]
-What's your worst?
-Huh?
What do you mean, worst?
That one that's planted roots,
kept you up at night,
popped into your head on
Christmas morning.
Don't you want a break?
Isn't that the point
of this thing?
Can we talk about
something else?
How could we?
-Mine's "Funky Town."
-Oh, yeah.
What's "Funky Town"?
It's a torture tape.
Super
popular disco soundtrack.
Skin everywhere.
It's disgusting...
It actually happened
like 10 minutes away
from where I grew up.
That's why it bothered me,
'cause this shit is closer
than you think.
And you?
My brother was a Marine,
so...
anything with soldiers...
really gets me.
-I'm sorry, that's sad.
-No, don't be sad.
He was a fucking...
a fucking... he...
Paul?
I don't know. I guess... I
don't have one yet.
-Not like you guys.
-Then get out!
And we all know
what Daisy's is, so...
how about we talk about
literally anything else?
Okay, sure, like what?
All right, girl,
I think I'm going to go.
-I'm going to stay.
-You're drunk.
I know, that's why I'm going
to stay.
Okay, so have fun, be safe,
and if Bob starts looking
fuckable, leave immediately.
-Bye.
This is why porn
is a good thing.
People get nasty urges, and
then instead of acting on them,
you watch a video,
and then like magic,
the nastiness is gone.
Well, what if the opposite
happens and you watch a video
and the nastiness sneaks in?
What do you do then?
I don't know.
Watch another video.
But everybody keeps saying
that it's fake, but does it
even fucking matter?
Because it's all I can think
about, and I can't shut the
fuck up about it.
[Daisy sighs]
This ticket had two million
views before I deleted it.
That's two million
people getting off
on someone else's pain.
Violence goes viral.
Always has, always will.
[dismissive laugh]
Look, I know the video you're
talking about.
You did a good thing
taking it down.
You've watched that video?
It popped up in my feed.
Out of nowhere?
You know how these things go.
We have no control over what
we see.
Right.
So, uh, I'm about to lock up,
but I'd be happy
to continue this conversation
elsewhere if you want.
No, thank you.
Come on.
All this talk of porn, and it
didn't put you in the mood?
Well, I guess it did.
In a way.
-Should I get rough?
-Yes, please.
How rough?
As rough as you want.
Okay.
Aah! Fuck!
What do you--? Aah!
Wait! Aah! Oh, God! Aah!
Stop! Aah!
Please! Wait! Stop! Stop!
Aah!
Aah! Stop! Aah!
Wait! Stop!
[sharp cry]
[Daisy snoring]
[no audible speech]
-The cops are here.
-Yeah.
What happened?
Someone working the overnight
shift had a stroke
or a seizure or something bad,
and nobody knew what to do,
which made a shitty situation
even shittier.
Oh, my God, that's awful.
Is he OK?
I mean, the management
said he'll be fine, but that's
what they always say.
They don't want to give us a
reason to stop working.
Where did he sit?
There.
[knocking on door]
Yes.
Money from the pool.
Give it to him or his kids or
whatever.
[door closes]
[cartoon music plays]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Are you hungry?
I can make you grilled cheese.
[sighs] No, thank you.
That's a very sweet offer.
I need to check something.
What happened
to your "no phones rule"?
This is just something with
work that I have to handle.
When's your dad back tonight?
10:30.
Um...
Okay, I have to go to my
office real quick.
-Right now?
-Yeah, yeah, just for one hour.
I'll put a movie on,
and I'll be back when it's over.
But I'll be by myself.
You'll be just for a little
bit. I'll lock the door.
You will be totally fine,
I promise.
I know I'll be fine,
but I'll get bored.
Welcome.
This is it. We got
some coffee over there,
some candy and stuff here.
And that's my
favorite corner right there.
Where is everybody?
On the way.
First off, sign these
and no stage names, alright.
Everything's got to match
your driver's license exactly.
We do everything above
board here.
Also, do you know this guy? He
owes me money for my license.
Oh, there's no phones
allowed in here.
Sorry. Company policy.
Okay, I'll go put it in my car.
Yeah, well that one's locked.
It closes automatically.
We can't have people just
coming in and out
of here like that
while the cameras are rolling,
so we keep it locked.
Okay, can you unlock it for me?
Not until you signed the forms.
I'm not signing anything.
Do you want some socks for
those cold feet?
[light laughter]
No, seriously though, I mean
if you leave without finishing
your paperwork,
I can't let you back in.
Why?
What's the other option?
Sign forms, hand me your
phone, and make two-fifty?
I choose door number one.
Have a great evening then,
beautiful.
[door buzzes]
[soft gasps]
[spray hisses, man cries out]
Aaahhh!
[coughing]
[cartoon audio plays]
Violet.
Hi.
[knocking on door]
-You left my 10-year-old alone?!
-I'm so sorry.
Sorry doesn't really cut it.
You weren't here!
And you didn't bother to text
me, which is both selfish
and fucking stupid.
What can I do to make it right?
Nothing.
[retches]
[line ringing]
[woman] Please leave
a message at the tone.
[beep]
Hi, it's Daisy.
Um, calling you back finally.
Sorry, it took me
ten whole years to do that.
Um, I wanted to see if you
were busy this weekend
and if you wanted to hang out.
Um, yeah.
So I'll be waiting to hear
from you, or not.
So, either way is good.
Okay, uh, hope you're having
a good one. All right, bye.
A patient
with AB negative blood type
cannot receive transfusions
from which blood types?
AB negative recipients
are positive incompatible,
so A positive, B positive,
AB positive, and O positive.
Correct. Ten points!
Is it bad that I don't know my
own blood type?
That's not ideal.
Well, shit.
Oh, that is disgusting.
[chuckles] What is it?
Decubitus ulcers?
Oh, those can get nasty.
Yeah, I could never do this.
I'm already traumatized.
Well, I don't know if I can do
it either. Right now I'm just
looking at pictures.
Well, I believe in you.
[faint, distant hammer pounding]
Did you hear that?
My neighbor does chores
on the weekend.
[faint, distant hammer pounding]
I can't listen to this.
Uh...
You get used to it.
Mm-hmm.
[faint, distant hammer pounding]
[hammer pounding]
[woman screams]
-No!
-Where are you going?
Tell this guy enough with the
handyman shit for the day!
-Why?
-Because it's driving me
fucking crazy!
Hello! Stop, fuck off.
There are people in here.
Stop it, asshole! Fuck you!
Are you okay?
[sighs]
I am now.
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah, you can have sex
with me, so I know that I can.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
[door slams]
Hey. All right,
where did you get those?
-Online.
-That simple, huh?
That simple.
Can I try one?
Sure. They're from a shitty
website, so...
they're probably sugar pills,
and they don't do anything,
but yeah.
-Can I try two, then?
-Sure.
Yeah.
Thank you.
-You should swallow the pills.
-That's just how I do it.
Yeah.
I miss you too.
Can I talk to Mommy?
[speaking native language]
[overlapping social media audio]
[dog whimpering in video]
[blows land]
[dog whimpering]
[weeping softly]
Well, you left in a hurry.
I did.
Joy was pissed.
I, uh... found a name.
Look, I don't know what you're
planning on doing with it,
and...
to be honest,
I don't want to know.
But if you think it's gonna
help in some way, so be it.
Just, uh...
Don't get hurt. Alright?
[bottle cap clatters]
[mysterious music rises]
[indistinct voice speaking]
Once ground zero...
[voice continues]
Just a reminder: that guy's
banned from pretty much
every platform.
Enjoy looking at him.
Okay.
And, by the way,
clean your neck, please.
Okay.
Not sure what that has to do
with anything.
[laughs] She's starting
to fucking lose it.
[muttering]
Holy shit.
You know what?
I don't think anyone is
going to recognize you.
You did.
Yeah, 'cause I was there, I
remember what you were wearing.
I can barely see your face
in the video.
[sighs]
[worried sigh]
So was it like kind of
self-defense or kind of?
No.
[no audible speech]
[Bob]
No?
No.
Okay. What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
It's your ticket, not mine.
It doesn't break
any of our rules,
so deleting it might bring
more attention.
I don't want to get you
into any trouble.
Maybe I deserve
to be in trouble.
Daisy, it's not you.
It's this fucking place,
it's not you.
It's got a lot of views. The
guy never filed a police report.
I checked, so you're probably
in the clear.
Still, though,
it's so fucking ugly.
"Girls boss destroys."
[light chuckle]
[Bob] Yeah, it's ugly.
[woman cries out]
I went on a date...
or I tried to.
But I got upset, and I left.
We're-we're supposed to talk
about work-related issues.
Yes, I left because of a ticket.
Okay, and what specifically
about this ticket
made you do that?
It bothered me.
Can you explain why?
Sometimes vocalizing an image
stuck in your head
can help root it out.
Well, you make that sound easy.
Just give it a go.
Um...
Mmm. People want to hurt people.
Okay, so in this video there
was an act of violence.
Yes, and it made me want to
hurt someone too.
I see.
You know, sometimes
when I go for a run, um,
to pump myself up, I daydream
about getting into a fight,
defending my wife, punching
some jerk for accosting her.
It's quite a common fantasy,
but it's not a healthy one.
It's actually quite selfish
putting someone else
in a position of danger
to make myself feel empowered.
But if that actually happened,
you wouldn't be putting her
in danger.
You'd be protecting her from it.
Sure, but my point is,
in these situations,
we tend to ignore the victim
and focus instead
on the villain.
We funnel our energy
into revenge or justice
or whatever you want to call it,
and we develop a hero complex.
But you're not the hero here,
Daisy. This isn't some
detective story.
You're just a regular person
doing a regular job.
Yes, thank you.
But maybe the girl
in the video wants that guy
to suffer like she did.
It's what I would want.
[clears throat]
You have an impulse, yeah?
To take action,
which is a wonderful thing.
Unless that impulse is to do
something not wonderful.
-It is not an impulse.
-What is it then?
I try to forget, and I keep
getting reminded
over and over,
and I know it sounds crazy,
but it feels like the universe
is telling me:
"Go find this guy!"
because it feels like our
fates are intertwined,
and I can't feel free until I
fucking do something about it.
But that's simply not true,
Daisy.
How do you know that?
Because if it were true, you'd
be talking to him now, not me.
-[voice on telephone drones]
-[knock on door]
Just a sec, wait. What?
I quit.
Your employee contract
requires two weeks' notice
before resignation takes effect.
If you don't oblige,
we'll take it to court.
Two weeks it is.
[urgent music rises]
[urgent music continues]
No!
Fuck! No!
Fuck! Aah!
Poor guy.
[man]
Fuck!
[indistinct shouting]
[man shouts indistinctly]
[urgent music continues]
[urgent music slows]
Don't fucking do it, bro.
[woman screaming]
Okay, I get it.
[distant siren wails]
[door opens]
[man] Daisy Morris?
Tell me something
you learned at your last job.
Well, I was in tech,
and while I learned
nothing about computers,
it taught me a lot about people.
Because that's what the
internet is. It's just people.
And for a while my biggest
desire was to help these people,
which is why I wanted
to be a nurse.
[man] Yes, that's why many
young men and women
enter the field of medicine.
I'm sure you hear this
all the time, but...
we think we need to devote
ourselves to something
noble and altruistic.
Something that makes our lives
meaningful and important,
but this job taught me that
not everyone deserves...
help.
Some people deserve
the opposite.
I realize that's not the best
thing to say in a job interview,
but what I'm getting at is:
I have learned how to hold
myself and others to task.
That's a good skill. Very good.
Another thing I learned:
There are three types of people:
people who make the world
better,
people who make the world worse,
and people who watch.
Most people, they watch.
That's it. That's all they do.
I would rather be
one of the other two.
Let me make sure
I have this correct:
You'd rather make the world
worse than do nothing?
Yes.
Okay, now you lost me.
Well, bad things happen
no matter what.
And sometimes the only way to
stop a bad thing...
...is with another bad thing.
You know, I'm not sure I agree
with you there.
Well, I figured you wouldn't.
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
As interesting
as all this may be,
I don't quite understand how
it pertains to the question I
asked.
Or our meeting. Or
a career in your desired field.
Oh no, it's related.
Well, you might think so, but
I'm not seeing it.
Trust me, it's all related.
[sinister music rises]
[objects clattering]